consumerinjuryadvocates.com 2014-02-23

# Privacy

**Effective as of October 8, 2010**

Welcome to [www.consumerinjuryadvocates.com](http://www.consumerinjuryadvocates.com/), the website and online presence (the “ **Site** ”) of Consumer Injury Advocates (“ **Consumer Injury Advocates** ”, “ **we** ”, or “ **us** ”).  Consumer Injury Advocates respects the privacy of those who access and/or use the Site (“ **You** ”, “ **Your** ”, “ **User** ”, or collectively “ **Users** ”) and is committed to protecting the personally identifiable information we collect from You as You access and/or use the Site via the Internet, the World Wide Web, mobile networks, or any other communication methods now known or in the future developed.

THIS PRIVACY POLICY SET FORTH BELOW (THE “ **PRIVACY POLICY** ”) HEREBY INCORPORATES BY REFERENCE THE [TERMS OF USE](http://www.consumerinjuryadvocates.com/disclaimer.html) OF THE SITE AND IS INCORPORATED INTO AND IS SUBJECT TO THE [TERMS](http://www.consumerinjuryadvocates.com/disclaimer.html) THEREIN.  YOUR USE OF THE SITE AND ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE THROUGH THE SITE ARE SUBJECT AT ALL TIME TO THE PRIVACY POLICY AND THE [TERMS](http://www.consumerinjuryadvocates.com/disclaimer.html).  BY USING THE SITE, YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE PRIVACY POLICY AND THE [TERMS](http://www.consumerinjuryadvocates.com/disclaimer.html). 

### 1\. Definitions

**a. Automatically Collected Information**   
When You access the Site, we may send one or more cookies to Your computer.  A cookie is a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters that a website stores on Your computer that Your browser provides to a website each time You access the website.  Use of cookies is very common on the Internet. We use these cookies to identify prior Users and track usage of the Site. You can remove these cookies and modify Your browser’s settings to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify You when a cookie is sent.  Please review Your web browser’s “Help” file to learn the proper way to modify Your cookie settings. 

In addition, like many websites, when You access the Site, we may automatically record certain information from Your system by using different types of other common Internet technology.  This automatically collected information may include Your Internet Protocol address (or “IP Address”), a unique device or User ID, version of software installed, system type, the content and pages that You access on the Site, and the dates and times that You visit Site.

**b. Personally Identifiable Information**   
Consumer Injury Advocates only collects personally identifiable information that is voluntarily provided to us by Users. 

### 2\. The Way We Use This Information

**a. Automatically Collected Information**   
Consumer Injury Advocates uses cookies and other automatically collected information to identify prior Users, to track usage of the Site, and for analytical purposes to help us improve the Site and our business in general. We will provide this information to Affiliates and/or third parties to assist us in providing these functions. 

**b. Personally Identifiable Information**   
The personally identifiable information that Users voluntarily provide to Consumer Injury Advocates may be used by Consumer Injury Advocates and our Affiliates, including contracted third-parties for administrative purposes; for authentication purposes; to properly operate, maintain, and provide You with the features and functionality of the Site; to present You with promotions, advertisement, and opportunities which may be of interest to You via direct mail, email, phone, text, or sms; to enable our Affiliates and to assist us in operating, maintaining, and providing our Services and products to You via direct mail, email, phone, text, or sms; to enable us to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts/subscriptions entered into with You; to notify You about changes to the Privacy Policy or the Terms of Use, Site, or Service (if we deem it appropriate); to investigate and help prevent potentially unlawful activity or activities that threaten the integrity of the Site or Consumer Injury Advocates Technology; to investigate allegations of fraud or violations of the Terms; to enforce or apply our rights under the Terms or Service Agreement; to protect the rights, property, or safety of any of our Clients or others; to improve the quality and design of the Site and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing your preferences and trends; and/for marketing and business purposes. Consumer Injury Advocates RESERVES THE RIGHT TO, AND WILL, RENT, SELL, SHARE OR TRANSFER YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES FOR ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE PURPOSE IN ITS SOLE DISCRETION.

### 3\. Security of Information

Consumer Injury Advocates maintains our systems in accordance with commercially reasonable industry standards to preserve the integrity and security of Your personally identifiable information under our control.  We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information You Transmit to us, and You do so at Your own risk.  Once we receive Your transmission of information, we make commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems.  However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.   “Perfect security" does not exist on the Internet, and You use the Site at Your own risk.

### 4\. Children

Consumer Injury Advocates DOES NOT SELL PRODUCTS OR SERVICES FOR PURCHASE BY CHILDREN.  IF YOU ARE UNDER 18 YEARS OF AGE, THEN PLEASE DO NOT USE OR ACCESS THE SITE AT ANY TIME OR IN ANY MANNER. 

PROTECTING THE PRIVACY OF YOUNG CHILDREN IS ESPECIALLY IMPORTANT.  FOR THAT REASON, Consumer Injury Advocates DOES NOT KNOWINGLY COLLECT OR MAINTAIN PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION FROM PERSONS UNDER 13 YEARS-OF-AGE. IF Consumer Injury Advocates LEARNS THAT PERSONALLY-IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION OF PERSONS LESS THAN 13-YEARS-OF-AGE HAS BEEN COLLECTED ON OR THROUGH THE SITE, THEN WE WILL TAKE THE APPROPRIATE STEPS TO DELETE THIS INFORMATION. 

IF YOU ARE THE PARENT OR LEGAL GUARDIAN OF A CHILD UNDER 13 WHO HAS PROVIDED US WITH PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION, THEN PLEASE [CLICK HERE](http://www.sblys.com/1489a761d40623ab7fe7111279c5ef0f474a788dbf2428e38a50727eef319e48) TO HAVE THAT INFORMATION DELETED IMMEDIATELY.

The following are some resources that may help parents and legal guardians in monitoring and limiting children’s access to certain types of material on the internet. While Consumer Injury Advocates does not endorse these products, we provide information about them as a public service.

### 5\. Links to Third Party Sites

The Site may include links or references to other websites or services (“ **Linked Sites** ”).  Linked Sites are provided for Your convenience and information only.  Please be aware that Consumer Injury Advocates is not responsible for the privacy practices of such sites.  We encourage You to be aware of when You leave the Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.  This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by Consumer Injury Advocates. 

### 6\. Opting Out

Consumer Injury Advocates only collects information that You have voluntarily provided to us.   You may “opt-out” of having Your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when providing us with this information.  You may decline to provide personal information to us and/or refuse cookies in Your browser, although some of our features or services may not function properly as a result.

Should You no longer wish to receive newsletter and promotional communications, You may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing or calling us per the information in Section 11 of the Privacy Policy.   You may continue to receive email communications from us up to ten business days from the time we receive Your unsubscribe request. Please note that Consumer Injury Advocates can only control its own mailing list and policies.  Third party advertisers that maintain their own mailing lists may send communications that advertise our services, and You may need to contact these parties directly in order to stop receiving their communications. 

### 7\. Events Outside Of Ordinary Business Practices

IN CONNECTION WITH AN EVENT OUTSIDE OF Consumer Injury Advocates’S ORDINARY BUSINESS PRACTICES, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO A SALE, MERGER, CONSOLIDATION, CHANGE IN CONTROL, TRANSFER OF SUBSTANTIAL ASSETS, REORGANIZATION, OR LIQUIDATION, Consumer Injury Advocates RESERVES THE RIGHT TO TRANSFER, SELL, OR ASSIGN THE INFORMATION THAT WE HAVE COLLECTED FROM USERS.

Consumer Injury Advocates ALSO RESERVES THE RIGHT TO DISCLOSE USER INFORMATION IN THE GOOD-FAITH BELIEF THAT IT IS REQUIRED TO DO SO PURSUANT TO JUDICIAL OR OTHER GOVERNMENTAL SUBPOENAS, WARRANTS, OR ORDERS, OR TO DISCLOSE SUCH DATA TO A GOVERNMENTAL INSTITUTION THAT HAS ASSERTED ITS LAWFUL AUTHORITY TO OBTAIN THE INFORMATION. 

Consumer Injury Advocates ALSO RESERVES THE RIGHT TO DISCLOSE USER INFORMATION THAT WE BELIEVE, IN GOOD FAITH, IS APPROPRIATE OR NECESSARY: TO TAKE PRECAUTIONS AGAINST LIABILITY; TO PROTECT Consumer Injury Advocates FROM FRAUDULENT, ABUSIVE, OR UNLAWFUL USES; TO INVESTIGATE AND DEFEND OURSELVES AGAINST THIRD-PARTY CLAIMS OR ALLEGATIONS; TO ASSIST GOVERNMENT ENFORCEMENT AGENCIES; TO PROTECT THE SECURITY OR INTEGRITY OF THE SITE; OR TO PROTECT THE RIGHTS, PROPERTY, OR PERSONAL SAFETY OF Consumer Injury Advocates, OUR USERS, OR OTHERS. 

### 8\. NON-U.S. USERS 

FOR USERS VISITING THE SITE FROM THE EUROPEAN ECONOMIC AREA OR OTHER NON-U.S. TERRITORIES, PLEASE NOTE THAT ANY DATA YOU VOLUNTARILY PROVIDED US WILL BE TRANSFERRED OUTSIDE THE EUROPEAN ECONOMIC AREA OR SUCH OTHER NON-U.S. TERRITORY FOR USE BY Consumer Injury Advocates FOR ANY OF THE PURPOSES DESCRIBED HEREIN. ****

### 9\. California Residents

In accordance with California Civil Code Section 1798.83, California Residents may  “opt out” of having their information transferred to third parties for marketing by [clicking here](http://www.sblys.com/1489a761d40623ab7fe7111279c5ef0f474a788dbf2428e38a50727eef319e48) with such request to “opt out” or via direct mail to:  Consumer Injury Advocates Unsubscription Services, 8690 Aero Drive, Suite 115–34 San Diego, CA 92123. Please include name (s) and email address (s) you would like removed in your request.

### 10\. Change in Privacy Policy

By using the Site, you are accepting the Privacy Policy and the [Terms of Use](http://www.consumerinjuryadvocates.com/disclaimer.html). 

Consumer Injury Advocates reserves the right, in our sole discretion, to modify, alter, or otherwise update this Privacy Policy at any time. Such modifications shall be effective immediately upon posting. You are responsible for regularly reviewing the Privacy Policy. Your continued access to and/or use of the Site constitutes Your agreement to all such modifications.

### 11\. Contact Information

Consumer Injury Advocates  
8690 Aero Drive, Suite 115–34  
San Diego, CA 92123  

Consumer Injury Advocates © Chilay, LLC.
